Guide to the Beecher Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1806-1818, 1822-1849, (1850-1930), 1931-1948, 1964; Series I; 19' (46 boxes)
  - Beecher-Scoville Family Correspondence
    - Scoville, Annie Beecher
      - To A. B. S.:
        - Betts, Anna W.P., 1899 (Box 21, Folder 835)
        - Betts, C., 1946 (Box 21, Folder 836)
        - Bigelow, Charles E., 1890 (Box 21, Folder 837)
        - Bigelow, E. A., 1890 (Box 21, Folder 838)
        - Biggs, Charles Lewis, 1933 (Box 21, Folder 839)
        - Bishop, Louis (Box 21, Folder 840)
        - Blake, Eli Whitney, Jr., 1892-1899, undated (Box 21, Folder 841)
        - Bonet, Emilie, 1927 (Box 21, Folder 842)
        - Boston Public Library, 1910 (Box 21, Folder 843)
        - Bowers, Cornelia W., [1911] (Box 21, Folder 844)
        - Bowers, Emily. (Box 21, Folder 845)
          See: Box 22, Folders 874-880
        - Brains, S.M., 1902 (Box 21, Folder 846)
        - Brave, Ben, 1896 (Box 21, Folder 847)
        - Brennan, Jennie L., 1903, undated (Box 21, Folder 848)
        - Brewster, Margaret H., 1930 (Box 21, Folder 849)
        - Bridgemen, Marian, [1911], undated (Box 22, Folder 850)
        - Briggs, C.M. (Box 22, Folder 851)
        - Brooklyn Children's Museum Woman's Auxiliary, 1926 February 19 (Box 22, Folder 852)
        - Brown, Esther F., undated (Box 22, Folder 853)
        - Brown, Laura Carter, 1927 (Box 22, Folder 854)
        - Brown, Mary E. (Box 22, Folder 855)
        - Brown, Orin O. (Box 22, Folder 856)
        - Brown, William (Box 22, Folder 857)
        - Browne, Gertrude B., 1924 (Box 22, Folder 858)
        - Bryan, C. Braxton (Box 22, Folder 859)
        - Bullard, Alice M. (Box 22, Folder 860)
        - Bullard, Clifford H., 1928 (Box 22, Folder 861)
        - Bullard, Mrs. E.D., undated (Box 22, Folder 862)
        - Bullard, Elizabeth, 1908 (Box 22, Folder 863)
        - Bullard, Henry Beecher, 1927 (Box 22, Folder 864)
        - Bunnell, Catharine M., 1925 December 24 (Box 22, Folder 865)
        - Burn, Josephine H.F., 1934 (Box 22, Folder 866)
        - Byington, Elizabeth, 1887 (Box 22, Folder 867)
        - Cadman, Rev. S. Parkes, 1927 (Box 22, Folder 868)
        - Call, Mabel S., 1931 February 1 (Box 22, Folder 869)
        - Cameron, Edna Beam, undated (Box 22, Folder 870)
        - Camp Cotuit, 1925 (Box 22, Folder 871)
        - Canada, Dominion of, Department of Indian Affairs, Dep. Sept. General, 1915 October 29 (Box 22, Folder 872)
        - Carlile, Grace L., 1887 (Box 22, Folder 873)
        - Carter, Emily (Bowers), 1886 June-1887 August, 1885 December-1886 May, 1884 August-1885 Nov, 1883 April-1884 Jul, 1888-1893, undated (Box 22, Folder 874-880)
        - Chapin, Sarah H. (Box 22, Folder 881)
        - Child, Katharine B., 1883-1886, undated (Box 22, Folder 882)
        - Chisholm Susan K., undated (Box 22, Folder 883)
        - Claflin, Mary B., 1886, undated (Box 22, Folder 884)
        - Clark, John W. (Box 22, Folder 885)
        - Clark, L.S. (Box 22, Folder 886)
        - Coe, Kate Foote, 1908 (Box 22, Folder 887)
        - Coe, Lotta, 1925 (Box 22, Folder 888)
        - Cole, Jean Dean(?), undated (Box 22, Folder 889)
        - Coles, Franklin A., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 890)
        - Collins, Mrs. N.J.A., undated (Box 22, Folder 891)
        - Colonial Dames (Philadelphia Chapter), 1923 (Box 22, Folder 892)
        - Coman, Katharine, 1904-1914, undated (Box 22, Folder 893)
        - Commercial High School, Providence, R.I., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 894)
        - Commission on Interracial Cooperation, Stabilization Fund, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 895)
        - Condeland, Lucinda, 1901-1902 (Box 22, Folder 896)
        - Congdon, Nannie G.R., undated (Box 22, Folder 897)
        - Congregational Sunday School and Publishing Society, 1885 (Box 22, Folder 898)
        - Congregational Quarterly (London), 1928 (Box 22, Folder 899)
        - Congregationalist, The, 1898-1928, undated (Box 22, Folder 900)
        - Conklin, Rev. John W., 1899 (Box 22, Folder 901)
        - Connecticut Forestry Association, 1925-February 7 (Box 22, Folder 902)
        - Connecticut Indian Association, 1899-1908 (Box 22, Folder 903)
        - Connecticut Power Company, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 904)
        - Connecticut Prison Association, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 905)
        - Connecticut State Park and Forest Commission, 1924 July 29 (Box 22, Folder 906)
        - Connery, Mary, 1923 (Box 22, Folder 907)
        - Cooper, Susan (Sage) Fenimore, undated (Box 22, Folder 908)
        - Cornelius, C.P. (Box 22, Folder 909)
        - Cornelius, Lavinia (Box 22, Folder 910)
        - Cornelius, Sampson (Box 22, Folder 911)
        - Cornell, Martha, 1940-1944 (Box 22, Folder 912)
        - Cornish, Frances, undated (Box 22, Folder 913)
        - Cornwall, Connecticut, Office of the Tax Collector, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 914)
        - Couteau, John Gauthier, 1894 September-1896 March (Box 22, Folder 915)
        - Couteau, John Gauthier, 1896 June (Box 22, Folder 916)
        - Crocker, Caroline S., 1887 (Box 22, Folder 917)
        - Cronkbite, Anna B., 1901 (Box 22, Folder 918)
        - Cross, Alice, 1897 (Box 22, Folder 919)
        - Cummings, W.H., 1897 (Box 22, Folder 920)
        - Cunningham, John, 1891 (Box 22, Folder 921)
        - Dale, Robert, 1909 (Box 23, Folder 922)
        - Dana, C.B., [1885], undated (Box 23, Folder 923)
        - Darling, Mollie, [1911] (Box 23, Folder 924)
        - Davidson, Mrs. H.A., undated (Box 23, Folder 925)
        - Davis, J.B., undated (Box 23, Folder 926)
        - Davis, Maud Elizabeth, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 927)
        - Davis, William Stearns, 1928 (Box 23, Folder 928)
        - Dawes, Anna L., 1898-1911, undated (Box 23, Folder 929)
        - Day, Anne Bigelow, 1911 (Box 23, Folder 930)
        - Dean, Elizabeth M., undated (Box 23, Folder 931)
        - Dean, Nellie, 1890 (Box 23, Folder 932)
        - Devan, Harriet Beecher (Scoville), 1879-1886 Feb, 1886 April-1889 April, 1889 June-1893 April, 1893 October-1898 Jan, 1899-1913, 1927-1945, undated (Box 23, Folder 933-942)
        - Devan, Harriet (niece), 1905-1918 (Box 23, Folder 943)
        - Devan, Scoville Thomas, 1893-1918, undated (Box 23, Folder 944)
        - Devan, Spencer C., 1887-1893, 1889 (Box 23, Folder 945-946)
        - Dickinson, Greta, 1875 (Box 23, Folder 947)
        - Dickson, Mrs. E.E. (Box 23, Folder 948)
        - Dinsmore, Charles A., 1928 (Box 23, Folder 949)
        - Directors of Old South Work (Box 23, Folder 950)
        - Dodge, Grace Vernon, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 951)
        - Dodson, Mary T. (Box 23, Folder 952)
        - Doubleday, Page and Co. (Box 23, Folder 953)
        - Dutton, Samuel T., 1906 (Box 23, Folder 954)
        - Dwight School for Girls, 1926 April 3 (Box 23, Folder 955)
        - Eastman, Charybdis (Box 23, Folder 956)
        - Eastman, Julia A., 1884-1898, 1908, undated (Box 23, Folder 957-958)
        - Eastman, Sarah P., 1888, 1925, undated (Box 23, Folder 959)
        - Ellis, Emma C., 1900 (Box 23, Folder 960)
        - Ely School, Greenwich, Connecticut, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 961)
        - Emery, Lillian F., 1888 (Box 23, Folder 962)
        - Emmons, Helen B., undated (Box 23, Folder 963)
        - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 964)
        - Englander and Greenbaum, 1932 (Box 23, Folder 965)
        - Ewing State Bank, Ewing, Nebraska, 1905 (Box 23, Folder 966)
        - Farrar, Ellen W., 1922 (Box 24, Folder 967)
        - Farrar, Frances, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 968)
        - Ferguson, S.W., undated (Box 24, Folder 969)
        - Ferris, Rev. Frank Halliday, 1927 (Box 24, Folder 970)
        - Field, Clara, 1899 (Box 24, Folder 971)
        - Fielder, Henry W., 1895-1898 (Box 24, Folder 972)
        - Fielding, Frederick W., 1928 (Box 24, Folder 973)
        - First Congregational Church, Bristol, Connecticut, 1920 (Box 24, Folder 974)
        - First Congregational Church, Middletown, Connecticut, 1928 (Box 24, Folder 975)
        - Fisher, Adam B., 1905 (Box 24, Folder 976)
        - Fitts, Clara Atwood, undated (Box 24, Folder 977)
        - Fletcher, Alice C., 1900-1918 (Box 24, Folder 978)
        - Flint, Lydia A.P., 1911 (Box 24, Folder 979)
        - Foord, Josephine, 1907 (Box 24, Folder 980)
        - Foote, Edward Milton, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 981)
        - Foote, Margaret (fragment), undated (Box 24, Folder 982)
        - Ford, John C., 1912 (Box 24, Folder 983)
        - Foster, Kay, 1940-1941 (Box 24, Folder 984)
        - Frazier, George J., 1893-1901 (Box 24, Folder 985)
        - Frazier, George J. (fragment), undated (Box 24, Folder 986)
        - Frederick H. Stokes Company, 1909 (Box 24, Folder 987)
        - Free Public Library of Newark, New Jersey, 1910 (Box 24, Folder 988)
        - French, Carrie E., 1884 May (Box 24, Folder 989)
        - Frissell, A.S., 1929 (Box 24, Folder 990)
        - Frost, J.T., undated (Box 24, Folder 991)
        - Fuller, Louise (De H.), 1929 (Box 24, Folder 992)
        - Galt, Evelyn, undated (Box 24, Folder 993)
        - Garretson, Rev. John, 1927 (Box 24, Folder 994)
        - General Federation of Women's Clubs, 1923 May 21 (Box 24, Folder 995)
        - Gibson, Hamilton, 1926-1928 (Box 24, Folder 996)
        - Giddings, Franklin H., 1898 (Box 24, Folder 997)
        - Ginn and Company, 1899 (Box 24, Folder 998)
        - Glenn, John M., 1912, undated (Box 24, Folder 999)
        - Gold, Charles L., 1899-1927 (Box 24, Folder 1000)
        - Gold, Clara J., 1908 (Box 24, Folder 1001)
        - Gold, James Douglas, 1911 (Box 24, Folder 1002)
        - Gordon, George A. (fragment), undated (Box 24, Folder 1003)
        - Green Rainbow, Charles (Box 24, Folder 1004)
          See: Box 33, Folder 1448
        - Griffiths, Emma L., 1923 (Box 24, Folder 1005)
        - Griffiths, Gwen, 1887 (Box 24, Folder 1006)
        - Griggs, Elmer V. (fragment), undated (Box 24, Folder 1007)
        - Grinnell, George Bird, 1898-1899 (Box 24, Folder 1008)
        - Guild, Marion P., 1929-1930 (Box 24, Folder 1009)
        - Gulick, Charlotte V., undated (Box 24, Folder 1010)
        - Gummere, A.M., 1925 (Box 24, Folder 1011)
        - Gunnison, Herbert F., 1927 (Box 24, Folder 1012)
        - Hackett, Rev. Allen, 1943 (Box 24, Folder 1013)
        - Hague, Eleanor, undated (Box 24, Folder 1014)
        - Hale, Emily Baldwin (Perkins), 1883 (Box 24, Folder 1015)
        - Hamlin, Berthe P., 1917 July 6 (Box 24, Folder 1016)
        - Hamlin, Bryan, 1927 (Box 24, Folder 1017)
        - Hamlin, George S., 1900 (Box 24, Folder 1018)
        - Hamlin, Helen B., undated (Box 24, Folder 1019)
        - Hampton Normal and Agricultural Institute, 1893-1917, undated (Box 24, Folder 1020)
        - Hart, John F., 1910 (Box 24, Folder 1021)
        - Harveson, Mae, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 1022)
        - Hastings, Richard, 1894 (Box 24, Folder 1023)
        - Haughton, Sarah M., 1891 (Box 24, Folder 1024)
        - Hawley, Margaret Foote, undated (Box 24, Folder 1025)
        - Hazard, Caroline, undated (Box 24, Folder 1026)
        - Hazard, T. Pierrepont, 1925 (Box 24, Folder 1027)
        - Hempstead, Louise, undated (Box 24, Folder 1028)
        - Hempstone, Mabel H., 1921 November 2 (Box 24, Folder 1029)
        - Henry, Mary A., 1905 (Box 24, Folder 1030)
        - Hibben, Paxton, 1926 (Box 24, Folder 1031)
        - Hiden, Mrs. M.W., undated (Box 24, Folder 1032)
        - Higheagle, Robert P. (Box 24, Folder 1033)
        - Hill, David Russel, 1895-1896 (Box 24, Folder 1034)
        - Hill, George Rice, 1905 (Box 24, Folder 1035)
        - Hill, George W., 1892 (Box 24, Folder 1036)
        - Hillis, Annie P., 1911 (Box 24, Folder 1037)
        - Hodgkins, Louise Manning, 1927 (Box 24, Folder 1038)
        - Hoffmann, Eleanor, undated (Box 24, Folder 1039)
        - Hoffmann, Ralph, 1928 (Box 24, Folder 1040)
        - Hoit, Mr. and Mrs. E.B., 1910 (Box 24, Folder 1041)
        - Holbrook, Florence, 1902-1948 (Box 24, Folder 1042-1044)
        - Holbrook, Florence, undated (Box 25, Folder 1045-1052)
        - Holbrook, Florence (fragments), undated (Box 25, Folder 1053)
        - Holliday, Cecyl, 1910 (Box 25, Folder 1054)
        - Homer State Bank, Homer, Nebraska, 1905 (Box 25, Folder 1055)
        - Homiletic Review, 1927 (Box 25, Folder 1056)
        - Honyoust, Daniel B., 1893 (Box 25, Folder 1057)
        - Hopkins, Susan, undated (Box 25, Folder 1058)
        - Hopkins, Woolsey R., 1903 (Box 25, Folder 1059)
        - Horace Mann Schools Teachers College, 1902 October 3 (Box 25, Folder 1060)
        - Hosmer, Herbert H., Jr., 1940 (Box 25, Folder 1061)
        - Hotchkiss, Aurelia G., undated (Box 25, Folder 1062)
        - Hottinguer and Co., 1891 (Box 25, Folder 1063)
        - Houghton, Sara M. (fragment) (Box 25, Folder 1064)
        - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1928 (Box 25, Folder 1065)
        - Howard, Annie S.S., 1923 (Box 25, Folder 1066)
        - Howard, Hazel, 1921 (Box 25, Folder 1067)
        - Howard, John Raymond, 1906-1926, undated (Box 25, Folder 1068)
        - Howard, Susan Taylor (Raymond), 1897-1903 (Box 25, Folder 1069)
        - Howe, James Lewis, 1927 (Box 25, Folder 1070)
        - Howland, Edith A, 1898 (Box 25, Folder 1071)
        - Hoyt, Frank H., 1894-1895 (Box 25, Folder 1072)
        - Hulett, Anna, undated (Box 25, Folder 1073)
        - Hurlbutt, Emma, 1893-1902 (Box 25, Folder 1074)
        - Hurlbutt, Isabelle B., undated (Box 25, Folder 1075)
        - Hurlbutt, Nellie, undated (Box 25, Folder 1076)
        - Hurlbutt, Sophie L., 1886 (Box 25, Folder 1077)
        - Hyde, Elizabeth, 1897 (Box 25, Folder 1078)
        - Indian Rights Association, 1898-1922 (Box 25, Folder 1079)
        - The Indian's Friend (Box 25, Folder 1080)
        - Ishkahula, Matthew [Ankle, Matt.], 1896 January-1898 March, 1898 May-1899 Jun, 1900 March-1921 May, undated (Box 25, Folder 1081-1084)
        - Ishkahula, Matthew [Ankle, Matt.] (fragment), undated (Box 25, Folder 1085)
        - J.H. Hale Co., 1917 (Box 25, Folder 1086)
        - Jackson, Helen, undated (Box 25, Folder 1087)
        - Jackson, Ida Grune, 1887 (Box 25, Folder 1088)
        - D.R. James and Brother, 1902 (Box 25, Folder 1089)
        - Jeffery, Jeanie Co., 1887 (Box 25, Folder 1090)
        - Johns Hopkins Colored Orphan Asylum. (Box 25, Folder 1091)
          See: Box 19, Folder 768 Box 24, Folder 999
        - Johnson, A.J., 1902 (Box 25, Folder 1092)
        - Johnson, C.R., 1908 (Box 25, Folder 1093)
        - Jones, Eva L.S., 1926 (Box 25, Folder 1094)
        - Jones, Rev. Henry L., 1897 (Box 25, Folder 1095)
        - Jones, Sallie G., 1885 (Box 25, Folder 1096)
        - Jones, W.A., 1905 (Box 26, Folder 1097)
        - Jones, William, 1892 September-1895 Apr, 1895 July-1896 May, 1897 Jun, undated (Box 26, Folder 1098-1100)
        - Jones, William (fragment), undated (Box 26, Folder 1101)
        - Jones, William. (Box 26, Folder 1102)
          See: box 24, Folder 987
        - Judd, Jerome, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 1103)
        - Kaiser, Charles S., 1904-1905, undated (Box 26, Folder 1104)
        - Kane, Helen B., 1911, undated (Box 26, Folder 1105)
        - Kansas City (Mo.) Public Library, 1927 (Box 26, Folder 1106)
        - Kealer, A.H., 1928 (Box 26, Folder 1107)
        - Kelly, Louise and Bill, undated (Box 26, Folder 1108)
        - Kendrick, Helen F., undated (Box 26, Folder 1109)
        - Kennan, George, 1902 (Box 26, Folder 1110)
        - Kent, Edgar M., 1901 (Box 26, Folder 1111)
        - Keystone View Company, Inc., 1927 (Box 26, Folder 1112)
        - Kingsbury, Alice E., 1921 (Box 26, Folder 1113)
        - Kingsley, Ebenezer, 1896 (Box 26, Folder 1114)
        - Kinney, Sara T. (Box 26, Folder 1115)
          See: Box 22, Folder 903
        - Kitchel, Helen, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 1116)
        - Kneale, Albert S. (Box 26, Folder 1117)
        - Knox, Mary Alice, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 1118)
        - Kroger, L.J., 1924 (Box 26, Folder 1119)
        - Ladies Western Missionary Society, 1916 (Box 26, Folder 1120)
        - La Flesche, Carey, 1892-1894 (Box 26, Folder 1121)
        - La Flesche, Mitchell C., 1892-1903 (Box 26, Folder 1122)
        - Lambert, Jesse B., 1895 (Box 26, Folder 1123)
        - La Mere, Oliver. (Box 26, Folder 1124)
          See: Box 33, Folder 1480
        - Larrabee, C.F. (Maj.) (Box 26, Folder 1125)
          See: Box 33, Folders 1438-1440
        - Lasell Seminary for Young Women, Auburndale, Massachusetts, 1922 (Box 26, Folder 1126)
        - Learned, Emily C., 1925 (Box 26, Folder 1127)
        - Leavens, Frances D., undated (Box 26, Folder 1128)
        - Lee, Alonzo, 1897 (Box 26, Folder 1129)
        - Leighton, Ruth, undated (Box 26, Folder 1130)
        - Leupp, Francis E., 1910 (Box 26, Folder 1131)
        - Leupp, Francis E. (Box 26, Folder 1132)
        - Lewis, James E., 1893 (Box 26, Folder 1133)
        - Lightbuer, Caroline, undated (Box 26, Folder 1134)
        - Lockwood, Florence, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 1135)
        - Long, Bryant Alden, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 1136)
        - Long, Fanny Bancroft, 1911-1912, undated (Box 26, Folder 1137)
        - Longtail, Philip, 1893 (Box 26, Folder 1138)
        - Lord, Mary P., 1898-1899, undated (Box 26, Folder 1139)
        - Lord, [Mary], 1934 June 26 (Box 26, Folder 1140)
        - Lord, Mary P. (fragment), undated (Box 26, Folder 1141)
        - Louisiana Purchase Exposition, Board of Lady Managers, 1904 (Box 26, Folder 1142)
        - Lovell, Lydia (fragments), 1947 (Box 26, Folder 1143)
        - Lowther, Sarah V., undated (Box 26, Folder 1144)
        - Lull, Robert W., 1927 (Box 26, Folder 1145)
        - Lyons, Laura, 1888 (Box 26, Folder 1146)
        - MacCarty, Mattie E., 1885 (Box 26, Folder 1147)
        - McElroy, Margaret J., undated (Box 26, Folder 1148)
        - MacKenzie, Mr. & Mrs. William, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 1149)
        - MacMillan Company, 1898 (Box 26, Folder 1150)
        - Madden, Bessie, 1912 (Box 26, Folder 1151)
        - A.N. Marquis & Co., 1919 (Box 26, Folder 1152)
        - Marsden, Edward, 1907 (Box 26, Folder 1153)
        - Martin, May D., 1879-1882 Apr, 1882 June-1887 Mar, undated (Box 26, Folder 1154-1158)
        - Massachusetts State Normal School, 1914 April 21 (Box 26, Folder 1159)
        - Mead, Frank, 1904 December 28 (Box 26, Folder 1160)
        - Mears. Rev. Charles Leon, 1928 (Box 26, Folder 1161)
        - Mears, Eliot Grinnell, 1928 (Box 26, Folder 1162)
        - Mercersburg Academy, Mercersburg, Pa., 1923 (Box 26, Folder 1163)
        - Merrill. F.W. (fragment), undated (Box 26, Folder 1164)
        - Merritt, Francis H., 1907 (Box 26, Folder 1165)
        - Meserve, Frances P., undated (Box 26, Folder 1166)
        - Metoxen, Nelson, 1894 (Box 26, Folder 1167)
        - Metropolitan Museum of Art, New York, 1910 (Box 26, Folder 1168)
        - Middlebury College, 1922-1924 (Box 27, Folder 1169)
        - Miller, Helen T., 1919 (Box 27, Folder 1170)
        - Miller, John R., 1905 (Box 27, Folder 1171)
        - Milligan, Mary, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 1172)
        - Mills, Mary, 1891 (Box 27, Folder 1173)
        - Milton, George F., 1928 (Box 27, Folder 1174)
        - Miner, Lilian B., undated (Box 27, Folder 1175)
        - Mitchell, Grace M., 1926 (Box 27, Folder 1176)
        - Moffatt, Thomas C., 1919 (Box 27, Folder 1177)
        - Mohonk Lodge, 1902 (Box 27, Folder 1178)
        - Montague, George, 1887 (Box 27, Folder 1179)
        - Moores, Emily B., undated (Box 27, Folder 1180)
        - Morgan, Martha Gold, 1918-1929 (Box 27, Folder 1181)
        - Morley, Louise, undated (Box 27, Folder 1182)
        - Morrison, C.P., 1887 (Box 27, Folder 1183)
        - Moses Brown School, Providence, R.I., 1925 (Box 27, Folder 1184)
        - Mosher, Thomas Bird, 1928 (Box 27, Folder 1185)
        - Mossman, H.A., 1901 (Box 27, Folder 1186)
        - Mott, Frank L., 1935 (Box 27, Folder 1187)
        - National Indian Association, 1903-1909 (Box 27, Folder 1188)
        - National Indian Association, Annie B. Scoville, Chairman, Loan Department. (Box 27, Folder 1189)
          See: Box 82, Folder 134
        - National Mutual Building and Loan Association of New York, 1893 (Box 27, Folder 1190)
        - National Probation Association, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 1191)
        - Naugatuck Women's Club Naugatuck, Connecticut, 1938-1939 (Box 27, Folder 1192)
        - Near East Foundation, 1937-1947 (Box 27, Folder 1193)
        - Neergaard, Anna B., 1890 (Box 27, Folder 1194)
        - Neergaard, C.F., 1890 (Box 27, Folder 1195)
        - Nettleton, Grace Langdon, 1898 (Box 27, Folder 1196)
        - Newton, Jennie C., 1881-1882 (Box 27, Folder 1197)
        - Newton Centre Woman's Club, 1904 (Box 27, Folder 1198)
        - Niebuhr, Henry, 1905 (Box 27, Folder 1199)
        - Nunn, Nellie L., 1906 (Box 27, Folder 1200)
        - Nutt, Kate W., 1911 (Box 27, Folder 1201)
        - Ohle, Frieda Hoffmann, 1911 (Box 27, Folder 1202)
        - Ohlson, Mrs. H.J. Newton, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 1203)
        - Orr, Emily, 1885-1888, undated (Box 27, Folder 1204)
        - Outlook, The, 1898 (Box 27, Folder 1205)
        - Palo Alto Book Shop, Palo Alto, California, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 1206)
        - Park, Charles F., 1930 (Box 27, Folder 1207)
        - Park, Gertrude, undated (Box 27, Folder 1208)
        - Parker, Emma, 1890 (Box 27, Folder 1209)
        - Parker, Rev. Joseph, 1890-1897 (Box 27, Folder 1210)
        - Parkhurst, Alex, 1893 (Box 27, Folder 1211)
        - Parkhurst, Charles D., 1908 (Box 27, Folder 1212)
        - Pattee, Lottie A., 1900 (Box 27, Folder 1213)
        - Payer, Alex, 1897 (Box 27, Folder 1214)
        - Pearce, Clara Jeannette, 1904 (Box 27, Folder 1215)
        - Pedrick, Catherine, 1887 (Box 27, Folder 1216)
        - Pemberton, M. Bessie, 1888-1889 (Box 27, Folder 1217)
        - Picotte, Susan La Flesche (Box 27, Folder 1218)
        - Pine Hill Farm, 1914 (Box 27, Folder 1219)
        - Pinney, May M., 1884 April (Box 27, Folder 1220)
        - Pitt, Marian Edith (Perkins), 1881-1944, undated (Box 27, Folder 1221)
        - Platt, Mary Schanffler, 1925 (Box 27, Folder 1222)
        - Pope, Liston, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 1224)
        - Powers, Hale, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 1225)
        - Powless, Alfred, 1895 (Box 27, Folder 1226)
        - Powless, Ella M., 1896 (Box 27, Folder 1227)
        - Powless, Margaret J., 1898 (Box 27, Folder 1228)
        - Pratt, Martha Root, 1921 (Box 27, Folder 1229)
        - Presbyterian Advance, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 1230)
        - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., Board of Home Missions, 1905-1910 (Box 27, Folder 1231)
        - Prescott, C., 1916 (Box 27, Folder 1232)
        - Preston, Marguerite, undated (Box 27, Folder 1233)
        - Price, Mabel, 1888, undated (Box 27, Folder 1234)
        - Progressive Indian Association. (Box 27, Folder 1235)
          See: Box 82, Folder 135
        - Provide Society for Organizing Charity. (Box 27, Folder 1236)
          See: Box 21, Folder 841
        - Provost, William B., 1893 (Box 27, Folder 1237)
        - Quinton, Amelia S. (Mrs.) (Box 27, Folder 1238)
        - Ramage, Lucy B., 1919 (Box 27, Folder 1239)
        - Rand, McNally and Co., 1901 (Box 27, Folder 1240)
        - Raymond, Charles J., 1906 (Box 27, Folder 1241)
        - Raymond, John, 1905 (Box 27, Folder 1242)
        - Raymond, Rossiter Worthington, 1908 (Box 27, Folder 1243)
        - Reformed Church of America, Board of Domestic Missions, 1903 November 10 (Box 27, Folder 1244)
        - Richardson, Lyon N., 1940 (Box 27, Folder 1245)
        - Richmond, Frances, 1888 (Box 27, Folder 1246)
        - Riggs, Rev. A.L., 1905 (Box 27, Folder 1247)
        - Riggs, Frederick B., 1897 (Box 27, Folder 1248)
        - Riggs, Louisa Irvine, 1905-1907 (Box 27, Folder 1249)